jobzapply.com 2015-06-17

# jobzapply privacy policy | JobzApply.com

JobzApply.com is committed to protecting your privacy. Please read the Privacy Statement Below.

Collection Of Personal Information:

We May collect your personal information such as email ID & your name to provide you better service. JobzApply.com will protect you personal information. We won’t sell or distribute your personal details to a third party. We won’t email you unless you’ve asked us to. You can instantly unsubscribe from our mailing list at any time – by clicking the unsubscribe link. We take reasonable precautions to ensure the protection of personal information

Use of Cookies  
Other information may be sent to your computer in the form of an Internet “cookie” to allow our Web server to better serve files to you. The cookie is stored on your hard drive, along with others sent from other Web sites. Our server may request that your computer return a cookie to it, so that it “remembers” you as a user, and can better serve you. These return cookies, which may contain information supplied by you, are never stored on our server. Your Web browser can be set to allow you to refuse cookies. This will not lessen your ability to enjoy this Web site in any way. This information lets a Web site remember what state your browser is in. An ID is one simple piece of state information — if an ID exists on your machine, the site knows that you have visited before.  
Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.  
Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings.

Changes to This Privacy Statement  
We will occasionally update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our services. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how JobzApply.com is protecting your information.
